valfre.com 2014-05-23

# Privacy Policy - Site Security is Very Important to Us – Valfré

**Your Privacy and the Security of Your Personal Information is Very Important to Us**

VALFRE LLC. and its affiliates, value our customers and visitors to our Websites and respect your concerns about the privacy of your personal information and data security. Our Privacy and Security Policy (the "Privacy Policy") is intended to protect your privacy and provide you with a safe and secure experience in fashion, style and shopping. This Privacy Policy applies to our Websites hosted in the United States and to our fashion marketing and sales activities, including sales through our store locations. This Privacy Policy protects consumers providing information through our Websites and stores and is not designed to protect business information. By using our Websites or providing information to us at our stores, you consent to the collection and use of your personal information. In addition to reviewing our Privacy Policy, you should also read our Terms of Use for our Website. Your use of our Website constitutes your agreement to its terms and conditions.  

**Our Privacy Policy Will Change Over Time  **

****Because we continue to develop our Website and take advantage of technologies to improve the services we provide, our policies will change over time. We encourage you to refer to this Privacy Policy from time to time to stay abreast of our most current privacy policy practices. If you are a registered user of our Website, we may notify you by email of material changes to our Privacy Policy using the most current email address you have provided to us. Your continued access and use of our Website will constitute your acceptance of any changes or revisions to our Privacy Policy.

**The Type of Information our Websites and Stores Collect About You**

****VALFRE LLC. collects information that you provide to us or that we learn about you from your use of our Website or shopping at our stores. We receive and store information you enter on our Website, provide to us at our stores, or give to us in any other way. For example, you may provide information to us when you register with our Website, sign-in, search, add items to your shopping cart, pay for an item, participate in a survey, contest or promotion, apply for a job, request to receive our marketing materials, or communicate with VALFRE LLC's customer service. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, phone number, email address, payment card information, and personal shopping and product preferences. In applying for a job with us, you may provide to us your name, address, phone number, email address, previous work experience, references and other personal information about your background and experience. 

We also automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you visit our Website. We might also receive information about you from other sources, such as in providing you special offers that we think will be of interest, and we may add that information to our account information.

**How VALFRE Clothing Uses Information About You**

****We use information we have collected about you to provide you with the very best shopping experience and the most current fashion clothing and accessories.   **We do not sell your personal information to third parties for any reason.**  We do not disclose your personal information to unaffiliated third parties, or to our affiliates, who may want to offer you their own products and services unless you have requested or authorized us to do so.

We may share your personal information with third parties or affiliates of VALFRE LLC. where it is necessary for us to complete a transaction you authorized or perform some other activity you have asked us to do.

We may share your personal information with third parties or affiliates of VALFRE LLC. with whom we have contracted to perform services on our behalf. All companies that act on our behalf are contractually obligated to keep the personal information we provide to them confidential and to use the personal information we share only to provide the services we ask them to perform. 

We may disclose personal information about our customers as permitted or required by law, such as in connection with a subpoena or similar legal process, or in connection with a merger, acquisition or bankruptcy, as discussed further below. We may disclose information about you to protect against fraud and other crimes and to enforce our contracts with you. 

We try to provide you with the information you need to make informed reasonable choices with respect to how our Website uses or shares your information. VALFRE LLC. collects and uses personal information from you in several ways:

  * **Website usage.**  VALFRE LLC.’s authorized service providers may observe activities, preferences and transactional data (such as your IP address, browser type and operating system) relating to your use of our Website. We may use this collected or logged information in order to provide better service, to facilitate our customers' use of the website, to track usage of the website, and to address security hazards. VALFRE LLC., or one of VALFRE LLC.’s authorized service providers, may use this information to track aggregate traffic patterns throughout our Website for VALFRE LLC.’s internal analysis.
  * **Online Transactions.**  We collect information about you when you shop on our website. You may visit our site without registering, but if you wish to add merchandise to your shopping cart, or use other special features offered on our site, you will need to provide us with certain information, including your name, address, phone number and email address, to open an account with us. We will assist you in creating a user id and a password to protect your account information.
  * **Store Transactions.**  We collect information about you when you purchase merchandise in our stores or sign-up in our stores to receive our marketing materials or apply for a job.

**Our Security Practices**

****Our internal data security policies restrict access to customers' personal information to authorized employees. Authorized employees may use our customers' personal information for VALFRE LLC. business purposes only. Our employees are bound by VALFRE LLC. policies that require them to maintain the confidentiality of our customers' personal information. Employees who violate these requirements are subject to disciplinary action, up to and including termination.

We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that are designed to guard our customers' personal information. For example, for the security of your online visit to our Website, we may make use of firewall barriers, encryption techniques and/or authentication procedures. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be absolutely secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, VALFRE LLC. cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk. In the event of a breach of the confidentiality or security of your personal information, we will notify you as necessary and to the extent possible so you can take appropriate protective steps. Unless you indicate otherwise, we may notify you under such circumstances using the email address you provided to us when you registered with our Website.

**What are Cookies and How Does our Website Use Them?**

****We may use "cookies" to collect or log certain information. A cookie is a small piece of information that a website stores on a personal computer and which it can later retrieve. We may use cookies for some administrative purposes, for example, to store our customers' preferences for certain kinds of products. The cookies will not contain information that will enable anyone to contact our customers via telephone, email, or any other means. If our customers are uncomfortable with the use of cookie technology, they can set their browsers to refuse cookies. Certain of our services, however, could be dependent on cookies and our customers may disable those services by refusing cookies.

**Links to Third Party Sites and Websites Containing our Websites Branding**

****Our Websites may contain links to third party sites. Please be aware, however, that VALFRE LLC. is not responsible for and cannot control the privacy policies of these other sites or their practices. We encourage you to read the privacy policies for these other sites, as they may differ from ours. This Privacy Policy applies solely to personal information collected by VALFRE LLC.

**Contact Preferences and Accessing Your Personal Information**

****You have choices when it comes to how VALFRE LLC. uses your personal information. When you register online with our Website or sign-up in our stores, you can choose not to receive information about merchandise, services and special promotional offers from us by direct mail and/or email. If you elect not to receive such product marketing information by direct mail or email, VALFRE LLC. may continue to contact you as necessary to service your account and process your transactions. You can change your preferences by following the instructions for opting out at the end of the marketing email, or by following the instructions for Account Information on the Websites or by contacting Customer Service at  [cs@valfre.com](mailto:cs@valfre.com), or calling 1-888-559-9777.

Keeping your account information accurate and up to date is very important so we can provide you with excellent service. If your account information is incomplete, inaccurate or not current, please follow the instructions for My Account on our Websites to correct or update your account information online, or you may contact Customer Service at [cs@valfre.com](mailto:cs@valfre.com), or calling 1-888-559-9777.

**Mergers, Acquisitions and Bankruptcy**

****If VALFRE LLC. should ever file for bankruptcy or merge with another company, or if VALFRE LLC. should decide to buy another business, or sell or reorganize part or all of VALFRE LLC.’s business, VALFRE LLC. may be required to disclose your personal information to prospective or actual purchasers and other parties. It is VALFRE LLC.’s practice to obtain appropriate protections for information disclosed in these types of transactions. VALFRE LLC. cannot, however, guarantee that VALFRE LLC.’s Privacy Policy will remain unchanged if VALFRE LLC. is sold or merges with another company.

**Our Website is Not for Use by Children**

****Children are not eligible to use our Website. We ask that minors (under the age of 18) only use our Website in conjunction with your parents or guardians. Children under 13 years of age should not send any information about themselves to VALFRE LLC. If a child under 13 submits information through any part of our Websites, and VALFRE LLC. becomes aware that the person submitting the information is a child, we will attempt to delete this information as soon as possible. Because we do not knowingly collect any personal information about children under 13, we do not use or disclose such information to third parties.

**What else should I know about my privacy?**

****You should be careful to maintain the secrecy of your passwords and/or account information and be responsible about protecting your personal information and identity whenever you are online.

LLC.LLC.
